Keep your eye on the ball.
The Comebacks is a comedy film directed by Tom Brady.
Out-of-luck coach Lambeau Fields takes a rag-tag bunch of college
misfits and drives them towards the football championships.
In the process, this life-long loser discovers that he is a winner after all by redeeming himself, saving his
relationship with his family and friends, and finding that there is indeed, no "I" in "team"!
Freddie Wiseman/Narrator, played by Carl Weathers.
Lambeau "Coach" Fields, played by David Koechner.
Barb Fields, played by Melora Hardin.
Lance Truman, played by Matthew Lawrence.
Michelle Fields, played by Brooke Nevin.
Mr. Truman, played by Nick Searcy.
The Comebacks is a 2007 American satirical comedy film
directed by Tom Brady and story by Andrew Jacobson.
This film is a parody of the clichés and plots of the sports film genre.
It parodies 21 popular sports films along with historical real world sports events, credible live
football action and excerpts from The Onion Movie inserted throughout the film.
In the UK, Greece, Finland, Australia and New
Zealand this film is called Sports Movie.
The movie was released to theaters on October 19, 2007.
It was partially filmed at the Cal State Fullerton Titan Stadium in Fullerton,
California and Shepherd Stadium at Pierce College in Los Angeles, California.
The film explores themes of sports, baseball, baseball bat, coach.
The tone is lighthearted.